Jason Chen

BLOCKCHAIN & PYTHON & CHATBOT ENGINEER

Profile

Passionate Blockchain Developer offering 5 years of relevant experience in Blockchain.

I have experience developing DeFi, DEX, DApp, Trading Bot, Token, autonomous systems and artificial intelligence. I am fluent in Cosmwasm.Cosmos,Solana,Rust, Solidity,Web3.js,Cosmjs,Terrajs, Python and JavaScript ,and have worked on a variety of projects as a consultant, helping clients achieve their goals. I am also keen on several JavaScript and Python web frameworks like Vue, React, Django and Flask

I am a life-long learner and is looking forward to working on exciting and challenging projects. I am continuously trying to improve, learn more and gain new experiences.

With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team setting.

Looking for a Blockchain Developer job within a forward-moving company.

Employment History

Senior Blockchain Developer, Freelancer (fully Remote)

August 2020 — JANUARY 2022

- Multisig or validator based bridges, optimizes for high security and low cost with a medium latency of transfer
- Crosschain bridge smart contracts and Defi projects on the cosmos-based chain like Terra
- Crosschain Swap/Liquidity/Farming/Staking smart contracts
- Crosschain NFT Marketplace NFT Game(Genesis NFT)
- Deep knowledge of Terra protocols such as Anchor, Mirror protocol

Senior Blockchain Developer, Polarsync (fully Remote)

JANUARY 2019 —August 2020

- Trading bot with strong strategies (Front running, snipping, arbitrage, contract bot)
- NFT marketplace with Smart UI and high-end functionalities in Ethereum, Binance, Cardano, Solana, etc
- DEX and Centralized Crypto Exchange

Details

Hong Kong

Phone: +85236752895

Email:venus07250000@gmail.com Telegram: VersatileDeveloper Discord: Versatile Developer

Skills Hard worker **Computer Skills** Team Player **Excellent Communication Skills** Leadership and Teamwork Rust Cosmwasm Cosmos Python Solidity Web3.js Chat-bot JavaScript Ruby on Rails Ether.js

Languages

English

- Advanced Trading Platform (Stocks, CFD, Forex, Option, Features...)
- · Portfolio Tracking Platform
- · Multichain Web and Mobile Wallet
- Crypto Betting and Casino
- Yield Farming Protocols
- · Automated Market Making (AMM) Protocols
- Flash Loans
- · Impermanent loss, governance tokens
- P2P/Pool Lending and Borrowing
- Crypto Collectible Platforms and Non-Fungible Tokens
- Custom dApps
- NFT Game Development

Senior Python Developer, Ebunch (fully Remote)

JULY 2018 — JANUARY 2019

- Supported large enterprise customers by implementing and deploying mission-critical chat-bots built with Rasa. Deployments use Docker, Docker Compose, Kubernetes, and OpenShift. Infrastructure a combination of on-prem, AWS, GCP, and Azure.
- Designed and implemented NLU data, dialog stories, rules, forms, and custom actions (Python) for industry-relevant demonstrator chat-bots.
- Extended Rasa Open Source (Python) available at https://github.com/rasaHQ/rasa. This is an open-source machine learning framework to automate text- and voice-based conversations: NLU, dialogue management, connect to Slack, Facebook, and more.
- Created and taught an online course on advanced deployment techniques with Kubernetes (https://www.udemy.com/course/rasa-advanced-deployment-workshop/).
- Implemented Python Asyncio in back-end APIs resulting in dramatically improved throughput rates.
- Created CI/CD pipeline that trains a Rasa bot, builds a custom docker image, stores the artifacts in AWS S3 and AWS ECR, automatically creates an AWS EKS cluster using the eksctl CLI, deploys Rasa with Helm, and Smoke Tests using Python.

Senior Python Developer, Mazama Media (fully Remote)

JANUARY 2018 — JULY 2018

- Developed ML models for NLP, including methods for domain adaptation, methods for automated feature selection, methods for optimization of F-measure. Applied models such as logistic regression, SVM, CRF for both classification and sequence tagging.
- Developed a machine learning model for classification of tweets as either rumor/not rumor in R.

Hobbies

Market Researching, Gaming, Sports

- Acquired in-depth knowledge in relational databases, ontologies, and linked data. Implemented a classification model written in Java, that automatically categorizes Wikipedia pages as either belonging to the topic "Food and Drink" or not.
- Experimented with topic models with LDA in order to help with a recommender system for a large publishing company.
- Built prototypes for training word-vectors embeddings and graph embeddings.
- Developed models for sentiment analysis for English and Bulgarian, in R and Java. The methods were supervised for English and unsupervised for Bulgarian.
- Acquired significant experience with automated and semi-automated integration of various RDF resources as DBpedia and Geonames.

Senior Blockchain Engineer, MY2BE (fully Remote)

JANUARY 2017 —JANUARY 2018

- Interfaced with several crypto-exchange APIs like KuCoin, Binance, Bittrex, Bitfinex, OKEx, Poloniex, Huobi, and CCXT.
- Used REST APIs and WebSocket APIs.
- Saved time-sensitive data into a Redis database and provided database clients to retrieve data through a simple interface.
- Developed asyncio implementations for asynchronous operations.
- Used cfscrape (a Python library) to bypass a Cloudflare anti-bot page.

Senior Software Developer, FIXER Inc., (fully Remote)

JANUARY 2015 — DECEMBER 2016

- Built a web-based intranet application to streamline the process of managing in-house training data within the organization.
- Worked closely with the project champion, stakeholders, and users to learn the business workflow and identify the pain points that could be eased with automation.

Senior Software Engineer, UPWORK (fully Remote)

JANUARY 2012 — MAY 2014

- Implemented features for the main site and internal applications using TypeScript, React, Redux, Python and SQLAlchemy.
- Improved and upgraded the development tooling and workflow for several projects (TypeScript & Python).
- Coordinated the scrum process and helped improve communication within and between teams as scrum master for two teams.
- Developed a blockchain explorer and cryptocurrency accounting system for Bitcoin and Ethereum.
- Implemented a method for efficiently tracking the flow of funds between different addresses.
- Deployed the system on DigitalOcean using Docker.

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, City University of Hong Kong

APRIL 2008 — MARCH 2011

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, University of Manchester, Manchester

APRIL 2011 — DECEMBER 2011